(Raj:)Great. Then she won't know I'm lying.
(Raj:)Let's see, what else can I tell you
about me that would make you like me?
(Howard:)Uh...
(Raj:)Oh, I love music.
(Raj:)Do you love music?
You really wanna ask her that?
Oh. You're right.
Heh, everyone loves music.
(Howard:)She says,
"Do you play an instrument?"
No, but when I was 6 years old...
(Raj:)...I tried to start a boy band
called Frankie Goes to Bollywood.
(Raj:)But I couldn't get any other boys
to join...
(Raj:)...so my parents asked the servants
to be my backup dancers.
(Raj:)Wait, when you sign servants,
don't sign it like I'm bragging.
(Raj:)Sign it in a way that I sound humble,
with just a hint of:
"That's right, I had servants."
- Do you hear yourseIf?
- Yes, but she doesn't.
(Raj:)So get signing, hand monkey.